export const jsQuizz = {
    "test": {
      "test_group": 1,
      "next_test_group": 2,
      "question": [
        {
          "question": "What is the purpose of a job interview?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 2,
          "answers": [
            "To socialize with potential employers",
            "To test your knowledge of trivia",
            "To showcase your qualifications and skills"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "How should you dress for a job interview?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 1,
          "answers": [
            "Casual and comfortable",
            "Formal and professional",
            "Loud and attention-grabbing"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What should you research about a company before an interview?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 0,
          "answers": [
            "Their mission, values, and products/services",
            "Their social media activity",
            "Their employee's personal lives"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "How soon after an interview should you send a thank-you note?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 2,
          "answers": [
            "It's not necessary to send a thank-you note",
            "Within a week",
            "Within 24 hours"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the best way to answer the question: What is your greatest strength?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 0,
          "answers": [
            "Mention a relevant professional strength and provide an example",
            "Talk about a personal achievement",
            "Express your modesty and skip the question"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "How should you handle a question about your weaknesses during an interview?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 2,
          "answers": [
            "Pretend you have no weaknesses",
            "Refuse to answer",
            "Mention a minor weakness and discuss how you are working to improve it in the question"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the purpose of a resume in the job application process?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 0,
          "answers": [
            "Providing detailed information about qualifications and work history",
            "Sharing personal hobbies and interests",
            "Listing personal references"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the importance of body language during a job interview?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 1,
          "answers": [
            "It has no impact on the impression you make",
            "It can convey confidence, interest, and professionalism",
            "It's only relevant if you're applying for a job in acting or modelling"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "How should you prepare for common interview questions?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 1,
          "answers": [
            "Ignore them and answer spontaneously",
            "Review common questions and practice thoughtful responses",
            "Wing it not worrying to prepare for it"
          ]
        },
        {
          "question": "You've just entered the interview room and two people are waiting to interview you. What do you do first?",
          "comment": "",
          "test_answer": 0,
          "answers": [
            "Shake their hands firmly, introduce yourself, and wait for them to direct you to a seat",
            "Greet them with a smile and wait for them to offer you a seat",
            "Sit down and wait for them to speak"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  };

  export const resultInitialState = {
    GP: 0,
    correctAnswers: 0,
    wrongAnswers: 0,
  };